bizchair.com 2006-12-20

# BizChair.com

|  |  |  |  |   
---  
|  |  |   
---|---|---  
|  |  To: |   
---|---|---  
|  | **Office chairs for the executive at BizChair.com** | CUSTOMER SERVICE | INFO | [VIEW ORDER](http://order.store.yahoo.net/cgi-bin/wg-order?bizchair1) |   
---|---|---|---  
  
|   
---  
|  |   
  
---|---  
|  Office ChairsOffice FurnitureStack ChairsSchool FurnitureHome FurnitureSale ItemsMedical Equipment and Seating  
---  

Featured Items & Closeouts-Great Bargains on Office Chairs!24 Hour and Call Center ChairsArtBand SeatingBanquet SeatingBar StoolsBenchesBig and Tall Office ChairsChair Mats and Floor MatsChildren's Computer ChairsCleanroom ChairsCommemorative College GiftsComputer ChairsConference Chairs & Conference TablesCreate Your Own ChairDecorDrafting Stools, Counter Height Chairs, and Lab StoolsErgonomic Task and Computer ChairsExecutive Fabric Office ChairsExecutive Leather Office ChairsFolding ChairsHome Office ChairsHospitality ChairsIndustrial SeatingKneeling ChairsLaboratory ChairsLa-Z-Boy Office Chair GalleryLumbar Support and Seat WedgesMassaging ChairsMedical Equipment and SeatingMesh Office ChairsMicrofibre ChairsNesting ChairsOrthopedic SeatingPlastic ChairsReception Furniture, Guest Seating, & Side ChairsReclinersRestaurant Seating & EquipmentSalon ChairsSealy Posturepedic® ChairsSide Chairs, Hospitality Seating & Lounge SeatingSofas and LoveseatsStack ChairsSteel Framed Office ChairsStoolsTablet Arm chairsTraditional Executive and Side Office Chairs  
---  
|    
---  

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._ _This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[ Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._ _**1\. Disclosure to Third Parties:** We will not disclose any personal information to any third party source at any time. All personal information is kept secure and never shared or sold to any third party.  
**2\. Acquisition of Information:** We do not acquire any more information about consumers than is required by law or otherwise necessary to provide a high level of customer service.  
**3\. Our Employees and Privacy:** We train all our employees about the importance of privacy and give access to information about consumers only to those employees who require it to perform their jobs.  
**4\. Security Measures:** We make access to privacy sensitive information subject to rigorous procedural controls, consistent with legal requirements and the demands of customer service. We use the highest levels of encryption available for all credit card transactions.  
**5\. Transaction Server:** We use external transaction and processing servers to ensure maximum credit card and personal information security._

If you are uncomfortable ordering online, please click [here](http://lib.store.yahoo.net/lib/bizchair1/mail.pdf) to download a "mail order" form. Adobe Acrobat is required to view the document. To get it click the icon below.

Office Chair Bestsellers | [ Home](http://www.bizchair.com/ "Buy your office chair at BizChair.com") | Info | Search | Privacy Policy | Site Index | Preferred Sites | [View Order](http://order.store.yahoo.net/cgi-bin/wg-order?bizchair1)  

Questions? Comments? Problems? Customer Service  
Phone: 1-800-924-2472 | Fax: 770-509-3673 | 1325 Chastain Road, Suite 400, Kennesaw, GA 30144  
Copyright 2001-2006 by [Belnick Inc.](http://www.bizchair.com/ind.html) All Rights Reserved.
